lenpenzo.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy – Len Penzo dot Com

If you require any more information or have any questions about this privacy policy, please feel free to contact me by email at Len@LenPenzo.com.

At Len Penzo dot Com, the privacy of my visitors is of extreme importance to me. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by Len Penzo dot Com and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, Len Penzo dot Com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Some advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. My advertising partners include Google Adsense and, at times, may include other advertisers.

We may allow third-party companies that use tracking technologies, such as cookies or pixels, to record IP information about users who visit or interact with our website. This website does not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Len Penzo dot Com send cookies directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies may also be used by third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

This web site has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. This web site’s privacy policy does not apply to, and I cannot control the activities of such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Contest Rules**

No purchase necessary. Anyone under 18 must have their parents’ permission to enter. The odds of winning depend on the number of entries received or the number of votes that each entry receives. You become officially entered in a contest once Len Penzo dot Com has received the specified comment, email or entry form. To be considered valid, all entries must be received by the specified contest deadline. No responsibility is assumed for lost, stolen, delayed, and/or misdirected entries, or entries not otherwise received due to technical or any other reasons. After the contest winner has been announced, winners have seven (7) days to respond back to accept the prize, or another winner will be chosen. Prizes are not transferable and not redeemable for cash. Payment of taxes imposed on the prize winner will be the sole responsibility of the winner. Any applicable PayPal or other wire fees are the responsibility of the winner. No warranties are implied or guaranteed with the prizes. Len Penzo dot Com is not responsible for prizes lost in transit. By entering our contests, you agree to abide by all of the rules. By entering our contests you also agree that any information you send to Len Penzo dot Com becomes the property of Len Penzo dot Com and may be posted and/or published, and none will be returned. All federal, state, country and local laws apply. Void where prohibited by law. Any additions or variations on these rules will be posted on the individual contest pages within Len Penzo dot Com.
